Hilda Mason, Board of Education 136
People's Archive, MLK Library
- Series 1
  - Mental Retardation News, 1977 (Box 209, Folder 30)
  - Newspaper Articles, 1977 (Box 209, Folder 31)
  - Elementary Teacher Education Programs which Offer Instruction in Nongradeness, 1971 (Box 209, Folder 32)
  - Formal Dedication - Dr. Charles R. Drew Blood Donor Center, 1977 (Box 209, Folder 33)
  - Advisory and Learning Exchange, 1977 (Box 209, Folder 34)
  - Community Gram Notice of Community Meetings on Proposed School Closing, 1977 (Box 209, Folder 35)
  - Alert Newsletter - Welfare Reform: It's Been Too Long Already, Undated (Box 209, Folder 36)
  - Budget Requests, Undated (Box 209, Folder 37)
  - Haddonfield Memorial High School Potential Course Offerings, Undated (Box 209, Folder 38)
  - Allocation of Resources SY 77-78, 1977 (Box 210, Folder 1)
  - Handicapped Kids Newspaper, Undated (Box 210, Folder 2)
  - DCPS System Conflicts Correspondence, 1977 (Box 210, Folder 3)
  - Washington Urban League, 1977 (Box 210, Folder 4)
  - Closing of Jackson School - The Center for the Visually Handicapped, 1977 (Box 210, Folder 5)
  - Curriculum Vitae - Annette H. Eaton, 1977 (Box 210, Folder 6)
  - Allocation of Resources SY 77-78, 1977 (Box 210, Folder 7)
  - Backus Junior High School Promotional Exercises, 1977 (Box 210, Folder 8)
  - Community Gram, 1977 (Box 210, Folder 9)
  - P.T.S Newsletter, 1976-1977 (Box 210, Folder 10)
  - Salute to William Bill Rice, 1977 (Box 210, Folder 11)
  - DC Street Academy Annual Report, 1976 (Box 210, Folder 12)
  - Eliot Junior High School Newsletter, 1977 (Box 210, Folder 13)
  - Adult and Continuing Education Annual Graduation Ceremony, 1977 (Box 210, Folder 14)
  - Applicants for War IV Vacancy, Undated (Box 210, Folder 15)
  - Community Gram, 1977 (Box 210, Folder 16)
  - National Committee Arts for the Handicapped, Undated (Box 210, Folder 17)
  - Hilda Mason for Chairperson Correspondence, Undated (Box 210, Folder 18)
  - Changes Proposed for the By-Laws of the Ward Four Coucil on Education, 1979 (Box 210, Folder 19)
  - Ward Four Council on Education Annual Meeting, 1979 (Box 210, Folder 20)
  - The Reading Management Team and Berkeley Public Schools Directory 72-73, Undated (Box 211, Folder 1)
  - Statements of Robert E. Petersen President of the Greater Washington Central Labor Council, 1977 (Box 211, Folder 2)
  - Statement of Milton A. Pilcher - Veterans Preference in D.C Employment April 7 1977 (Box 211, Folder 3)
  - Statement of Bruce I. Waxman - Public Hearing Concerning the Development of an Independent Merit Personnel System, 1977 (Box 211, Folder 4)
  - Council of DC - Public Hearings Concerning the Personnel System of DC and Bills Nos. 2-10/2-11/2-80, 1977 (Box 211, Folder 5)
  - Handwritten Notes, 1977 (Box 211, Folder 6)
  - Clauses and Sections Final Approval, 1977 (Box 211, Folder 7)
  - Local Twelve - American Federation of Government Employees - April 7 1977 (Box 211, Folder 8)
  - Statement of CLEO Michael - President - Council 211 April 7 1977 (Box 211, Folder 9)
  - Statement of Ethel James Williams, 1977 (Box 211, Folder 10)
  - Statement of Mr. William H. Simons Washington Teachers Union, 1977 (Box 211, Folder 11)
  - Statement of Hugh Hassan - President of Local 2725 of the American Federation of Government Employees, Undated (Box 211, Folder 12)
  - Statement of Dr. Sydney O. Hall President the Federal City College Faculty Association, Undated (Box 211, Folder 13)
  - Statement of Major Travis - National Vice-President 14th District American Federation of Government Employees, 1977 (Box 211, Folder 14)
  - Statement of League of Women Voters of DC Before the Governmental Operations Committee, 1977 (Box 211, Folder 15)
  - Statement of the Director of Personnel April 7 1977 (Box 211, Folder 16)
  - Issues and Options - Development of a Personnel System for DC, Undated (Box 211, Folder 17)
  - Memo - Comparison of Mayor's and Dixon's Personnel Legislation, 1977 (Box 211, Folder 18)
  - A Bill 2-10/2-11/2-80, 1976-1977 (Box 211, Folder 19)
  - League of Women Voters Request for Additional Financial Information Concerning the Personnel Systems Development, 1977 (Box 211, Folder 20)
  - Bill 2-10 and Bill 2-11 Independent Personnel System and Confirmation Amendments, 1977 (Box 211, Folder 21)
  - Statement of Betty Ann Kane Before Committee on Government Operations, 1976 (Box 211, Folder 22)
  - Statement of Hilda Mason Before the Committee on Government Operations October 20 1976 (Box 211, Folder 23)
  - Personnel Inventory Forms Returned by August 17 1977 (Box 211, Folder 24)
  - Statement of Director of Personnel Before the Committee on Government Operations Septemeber 7 1977 (Box 211, Folder 25)
  - Summary of Comments Received Concerning Committee Discussion Draft No. 1 District Government Independent Merit Personnel Act of 1978, 1977 (Box 211, Folder 26)
  - Comments on Committee's Discussion Draft No. 1 on Bills 2-10 and 2-80 (Independent Merit Personnel Act), 1977 (Box 211, Folder 27)
  - Tentative Agenda for Meeting of the Committee on Government Operations of the Council of DC 9/7/1977 (Box 211, Folder 28)
  - Committee on Government Operations DC City Council April 7 1977 (Box 211, Folder 29)
  - Police and Fire Retirement Practices, Undated (Box 211, Folder 30)
  - Merit System Administration Recommended Requirements, Undated (Box 211, Folder 31)
  - Independent Merit Personnel Act, 1977 (Box 211, Folder 32)
  - Tentative Timetable - Personnel Issues, 1977 (Box 211, Folder 33)
  - City Council Hearing on Bills 2-10/2-11/2-80, 1977 (Box 211, Folder 34)
  - March 31 1977 Memo - Issues and Options (Box 211, Folder 35)
  - Personnel Hearings Continue - Committee on Government Operations Schedules Roundtable Concerning Discrete Personnel Issues April 20 1977 (Box 211, Folder 36)
  - Public Hearing Concerning Allegations of Irregularities in the Management of DC Personnel April 7 1977 (Box 211, Folder 37)
  - Comparison of Features of Selected Labor Relations Programs, Undated (Box 211, Folder 38)
  - Testimony of IBPO - Local 442 Concerning Council Bills Nos. 2-10/2-11/2-80, Undated (Box 211, Folder 39)
  - Statement of DC Auditor - Independent Merit System, 1977 (Box 211, Folder 40)
  - Arrington Dixon Opening Statement Independent Merit Personnel System Public Hearing, 1977 (Box 211, Folder 41)
  - Allegations of Irregularities Personnel System, 1977 (Box 211, Folder 42)
  - Firefighters Association, 1977 (Box 211, Folder 43)
  - Testimony- Independent Merit Personnel System, 1977 (Box 211, Folder 44)
  - Shari B. Kharash - Board of Elections and Ethics Testimony, 1977 (Box 211, Folder 45)
  - Fiscal Year - 1976 Budget Correspondence, 1975 (Box 211, Folder 46)
  - Report of Committee on School Finance, 1974 (Box 211, Folder 47)
  - Ward Four Council on Education Newsletter and Memo, 1978 (Box 211, Folder 48)
  - State Plan of Operations for Food Services Program and Summer Food Program for Children in DC, 1977 (Box 211, Folder 49)
  - Public Hearing on Education July 10 1979 (Box 211, Folder 50)
  - Hearing on Affirmative Action Programs of the DC Government, 1975 (Box 211, Folder 51)
  - State Plan Operations - Summer Food Program for Children - 1978, 1977 (Box 211, Folder 51)
  - Project Proposals - Public Schools of DC (1 of 2), 1977 (Box 211, Folder 52)
  - Statement by Mrs. Virginia Morris May 6 1975 (Box 211, Folder 52)
  - Project Proposals - Public Schools of DC (2 of 2), 1977 (Box 211, Folder 53)
  - Resolution to Declare May 10 1975 "Human Kindness Day IV" (Box 211, Folder 53)
  - P.L 89-750 - ESEA Title I Institutional Care Division Programs Cedar Knoll - Oak Hill, 1977 (Box 211, Folder 54)
  - Resolution Proclaiming the Week of April 27- May 3 1975 as "Close-up Week" (Box 211, Folder 54)
  - Hearings on the 1974 Elections Process/Ward Boundaries/Reform of the Voter Registration Law, 1975 (Box 211, Folder 55)
  - Notes of Council Meeting of February 25 1977 (Box 211, Folder 55)
  - Mayor's Reorganization Plan #1 to Establish an Office of Services to the Aging, 1975 (Box 211, Folder 56)
  - Title I Comprehensive Program - 1978, 1977 (Box 211, Folder 56)
  - Statement of Mrs. Virginia Morris President of DC Board of Education Before DC City Council FY 1976, 1975 (Box 211, Folder 57)
  - The Citizens' Decentralization Proposal, 1973 (Box 211, Folder 57)
  - Action on Annual Budget FY 76 Regarding Methods for Considering the FY 76 Annual Budget, 1975 (Box 211, Folder 58)
  - April 14 1976 NSBA News for Immediate Release (Box 211, Folder 58)
  - Articles on Cancer, 1976 (Box 211, Folder 59)
  - Council Period One, 1975 (Box 211, Folder 59)
  - Hearing on Equalization and Title I Comparability Requirements District of Columbia Public Schools, 1975 (Box 211, Folder 60)
  - Resolution between DC Board of Education and the Superintendent of Schools, 1975 (Box 211, Folder 60)
  - City Council Hearing on Equlization and Title I Comparability, 1975 (Box 211, Folder 61)
  - Council Period One First Session Fourteenth Legislative Meeting April 8 1975 (Box 211, Folder 62)
  - Supplement to Hearing Notice Regarding Proposed Amendment to D.C Air Quality Regulation April 15 1975 (Box 211, Folder 63)
  - Dunbar Senior High Reprogramming, 1975 (Box 211, Folder 64)
  - Recommendation on Reprogramming Request for Wheatley Playground Facility, 1975 (Box 211, Folder 65)
  - Council Period One First Session Fifteenth Legislative Meeting April 15 1975 (Box 211, Folder 66)
  - Public Hearings on the Revenue Package Contained in the Fiscal 1976 Budget, 1975 (Box 211, Folder 67)
  - City Council Hearing on Equalization and Title I Comparability, 1975 (Box 211, Folder 68)
  - City Coucil Members Ask Mayor for Detailed Information on Political Surveillance by D.C Police, 1975 (Box 211, Folder 69)
  - Public Hearing Budget Priorities for FY 1976 February 26 1975 (Box 211, Folder 70)
  - Council Period One First Session Special Meeting March 7 1975 (Box 211, Folder 71)
  - Educational Accountabilty Legislation, 1977 (Box 212, Folder 1)
  - Police Regulation Bill, 1978 (Box 212, Folder 2)
  - Bill - Salary Act of 1955 (Box 212, Folder 3)
  - Dedication of Julius W. Hobson Sr. Middle School Correspondence, 1982 (Box 212, Folder 4)
  - Council Woman Hilda Mason April - 1978 Memos (Box 212, Folder 5)
  - Statement of Hilda Mson Before Budget Committee February 26 1975 (Box 212, Folder 6)
  - Betty Ann Kane School Finance Statement, 1978 (Box 212, Folder 7)
  - Hilda Mason Statement on Public Schools Budget, 1977 (Box 212, Folder 8)
  - Tracking Down the Dollars The Budget Process in DC Public School System, 1977 (Box 212, Folder 9)
  - Minority Report - F.Y 1979 Budget D.C Public Schools, 1977 (Box 212, Folder 10)
  - Report of the Committee on School Finance, 1978 (Box 212, Folder 11)
  - Public Hearing on FY '78 Second Budget Amendment and FY '79 Frist Second Amendment, 1978 (Box 212, Folder 12)
  - Ulman Correspondence - Tuition Tax Credit Bill Concerns, 1978 (Box 212, Folder 13)
  - Chairman Tucker Correspondence Comprehensive Plan for the National Captial, 1978 (Box 212, Folder 14)
  - Statement of Councilman Marion Barry on Teacher/Police/Fire Fighter Pay Adjustments, 1978 (Box 212, Folder 15)
  - Bill 2-293 - The School Transit Subsidy Act of 1978 Correspondence (Box 212, Folder 16)
  - Status of Agreement with Anacostia Community School Board, 1978 (Box 212, Folder 17)